{
    "id": "c4cff4e7843d4ac4abb5e8b726eeeb63",
    "title": "Infinitive With Or Without To Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "19830154465443a88692e41b1a8b32c5",
            "title": "Infinitives With Or Without To Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Need I ..................... the washing up?",
                    "description": "When need is used as a modal auxiliary verb, it is followed by infinitive with to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "to do",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better ....................... her what she wants.",
                    "description": "Had better is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "give",
                        "to give",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He began ......................... up off the floor.",
                    "description": "The infinitive is usually used with the marker to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "get",
                        "to get",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do I need ......................... any longer?",
                    "description": "When need is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "wait",
                        "to wait",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Need I ........................... for the drinks?",
                    "description": "When need is used as a modal auxiliary verb, it is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "pay",
                        "to pay",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don't let my children ............................ up very late.",
                    "description": "Let is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "stay",
                        "to stay",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They made the child .............................. the milk.",
                    "description": "Made is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "drink",
                        "to drink",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We both heard him ...................... that he was quitting.",
                    "description": "Hear is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "say",
                        "to say",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Could you help me ............................ this radio?",
                    "description": "Help can be followed by an infinitive with or without to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "fix",
                        "to fix",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was heard ............................ that she was disappointed.",
                    "description": "In passive structures, hear is followed by an infinitive with to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "say",
                        "to say",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Did you feel the ground .............................?",
                    "description": "Feel is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "shake",
                        "to shake",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was made ........................ back the money.",
                    "description": "Made is followed by an infinitive with to in passive structures. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "pay",
                        "to pay",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}